# **GARIMA SINGH**

Address: Kardmeshwarpuram Colony, Dev Lane, Near- DNS Lawn Kandwa, Varanasi-221106

Mob. 8127152267

email-garimasi593@gmail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Professional Executive Mentee with 2.6 years of experience in domain like, Human Resource (Trainee, Talent Acquisition & Executive level) Seeking a challenging position in a reputed organization where I can learn new skills, expand my knowledge, and leverage my learnings.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# HR Executive (C- core India Techno solution Pvt Ltd) – (Jan 2021 – Jun 2022)

- Managed the master database of employees, prepared, as required reports on employeerelated data to assist with the management and development of staff
- Done end to end campus placement hiring and conducted interviews.
- Took full charge of HR department, leaves and Attendance management, entry and exit formalities, grievances etc. And also ensure the working environment in the organisation
- Administrated on-boarding process for new employees and new hiring orientation programme, and providing training for the same

# **HR Trainee (SIMPL) - (Dec 2019 - Nov 2020)**

- Communicating with upper management and HR executives to develop and fulfil strategic hiring goals.
- Handle & Assisting departments with their recruitment needs through liaison with agencies/ advertisers Coordinating prospective candidates, interviewing them and administering offers
- Assisting with the production and implementation of HR policies and procedures

### **EDUCATION**

### **Master of Business Administration (Marketing & Finance)**

(United Institute of Management & Technology)

(Dec 2020 – June 2022)

- Post Graduated with 81% and among top five rank in college
- Done Dual Specialization with Marketing & Finance

# **Bachelor of Commerce -**

(Jun 2016 – Jun 2019)

(Mahatma Gandhi Kashi Vidyapeeth, Varanasi)

- Graduated with 70% and among top five rank in college
- Economy and Business Communication as main subjects

### **High School & Intermediate -**

(Mar 2014 – Mar 2016)

(St. John's Convent School, DLW, Varanasi)

- Passed High School With 75% with Science Stream
- Passed Intermediate with 72% With Commerce Stream

### **SKILLS**

Communication | Team Leading | Talent Acquisition | On Boarding | Operational Performance | Leadership | Campaign creativity | Agility | Strategic Thinking & Decisions | CRM

### **SOCIAL ACTIVITY**

- Working with Ideal women welfare since 2019 and did many workshops for welfare and programs and get recognition for the same
- Helped women to have basic knowledge and awareness about proper sanitation and malnutrition

### **CERTIFICATION**

- Mastering Customer Relationship Management by Google
- Mastering Strategic Management Skill by Adani
- Mastering Total Quality Management by Adani
- Project Management Planning to Execution by Google

# **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Completed Target within desired time and got Appraisal (C- core)
- Winner of Interstate Debate Competition (MBA)
- Member of Event Management at UIM